## **Taylor Bruno**

144 Lowrie Loop Mooresville, NC 28117

M 828.449.9781

taylorbruno895@gmail.com

taylormbruno.github.io

Profile

Prospective full stack web developer passionate about approaching challenges from all angles and excited to collaborate with others to create meaningful web applications. Before I began my journey in web development, I worked two jobs while attending college where I learned great time management and leadership skills which has already helped me with my work. Excited to put my excellent work ethic to use in a fast-paced, quality-driven team.

Experience

Student, UNCC Bootcamp; Charlotte, NC - Oct 2019 - April 2020

As a student of this bootcamp, I was able to create a portfolio of projects to gain the skills needed. I learned how to use client-side and server-side languages/frameworks to create web applications.

General Manager, MOD Pizza; Mooresville, NC - Aug 2018 - April 2020

As the general manager of this restaurant, I was able to use my team leadership and team building skills to meet deadlines and metrics set by higher ups. I also have experience with developing and training team and leadership members. This job required a large amount of team work and working across personal capabilities. Customer service was a major duty for this job.

General Manager, Papa Murphys; Mooresville, NC - Oct 2011 - Feb 2018

In this job, I built my skills from the above General manager position and really learned what it truly meant to be empathetic and approachable. With this position, I started as a team member and worked my way up to general manager, and along the way I learned how important accountability is for improvement. Learning this allows you to not hide away from mistakes, but to learn from them to avoid the same/similar ones in the future.

Education

University of North Carolina - Charlotte: Full Stack Coding Bootcamp, April 2020

Skills

Hard Skills	Soft Skills
HTML / CSS	Oral / Written Communication
JavaScript / jQuery	Problem Solving
Responsive Design	Organized
Version Control / Git	Data-Driven
Browser Developer Tools	Self-Motivated
Command Line	Customer Service